yoursonglyrics.com 2010-11-19

# YourSongLyrics.com - Privacy Policy

The privacy of our visitors to YourSongLyrics.com is important to us. 

At YourSongLyrics.com, we recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use and visit YourSongLyrics.com, and how we safeguard your information. We never sell your personal information to third parties. 

**Log Files**

As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL or Shaw Cable), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site. 

**Advertisement**

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. 

**What is the DoubleClick DART cookie?**

The [DoubleClick DART cookie](http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/faq.aspx) is used by Google in the ads served on publisher websites displaying AdSense for content ads. When users visit an AdSense publisher's website and either view or click on an ad, a cookie may be dropped on that end user's browser. The data gathered from these cookies will be used to help AdSense publishers better serve and manage the ads on their site(s) and across the web. 

**Please keep in mind:**

* Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site.  

* Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet.  

* Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).
